SHIREESH KULKARNI

SR. BUSINESS ANALYST

PHONE I (+91) 9860355377

EMAIL I shireesh87@gmail.com

LOCATION I Pune, INDIA

EXPERIENCE I 7 Years 0 Month

Key Skills

- FRD
- Stakeholder Management
- Agile
- Confluence
- JIRA
- Requirement Gathering
- Requirements Management
- User Stories
- Requirement Analysis
- Business Analyst
- Functional Analysis
- Use Cases
- Brd
- Business Analysis

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

Social links

 www.linkedin.com/in/shiree sh-kulkarni-0b156b48

Profile Summary

Business Analyst having demonstrated and proven experience in HRMS, Agri Tech,Retail, ERP domains. Possessing strong skills such as requirement gathering and analysis, Requirement documentation, project coordination, financial analysis, and product delivery. willing to put in optimum efforts in given assignments. Ready to learn and adapt to new environment.

Work Experience

Sr. Business Analyst globant 10/2022 - Present

Working as Business Analyst

Business Analyst

Capgemini Technology Services India Limited 01/2021 - 10/2022

1. Responsible for understanding Problem Statement of client 2. Analysing client's business requirements and processes through document analysis, interviews, workshops, and workflow analysis. 3. Communicating client's business requirements to technology team by constructing data and process models, Requirement Documents. 4. Creating and monitoring User Stories in JIRA 5. Creating project documentation in Confluence 6. Client handling and coordination

Business Analyst

Shivrai Technologies 02/2019 - 12/2020

1. Responsible for understanding Problem Statement of potential client 2. Analysing client's business requirements and processes through document analysis, interviews, workshops, and workflow analysis. 3. Communicating client's business requirements to technology team by constructing data and process models, Requirement Documents. 4. Performing Functional Testing 5. Monitoring development process 6. Client handling and coordination 7. Responsible for product delivery 8. initiating & monitoring Go-live process for each client.

Senior Associate

Paysquare Consultancy Ltd. 01/2017 - 02/2019

i) Responsible for Requirement Analysis of "Benefits Trust" Software. ii) Preparing Project plan and tracking execution time and deviations in the same. iii) Manual Testing of Same software. iv) Implementation of application. v) Client Communication and handling client requirements.

Management Executive SARA MANAGEMENT SOLUTION PVT LTD 04/2015 - 01/2017

i) Responsible for Requirement gathering and analysis for ???Online Application Portal???, which was deployed at client side. It included application process from employees, screening of applications at client admin end and then processing the same applications through in-house operations software. Performed manual testing for the same ii) Handling PF, Gratuity and Superannuation claim processing for Trusts iii) Responsible for all procedural activities related to PF, Gratuity and Superannuation Trusts. iv) Keeping accounts for above mentioned processes using Tally & in house accounting system. v) Preparing & maintaining Investment data for Provident Fund Trust vi) Preparing &

maintaining Fund Balance data for Gratuity & Superannuation Trusts. vii) Assisting in accounts finalization process. viii) Communicating and coordinating with clients on daily basis

Administration Officer

Jyoti Computer Services 08/2013 - 12/2014

i) Day to day administration duties. ii)
Counseling of potential students regarding various courses. iii) Teaching for basic operational level computer courses. iv)
Handling back office work.

Operation Executive

Edelweiss-Tokio Life Insurance Co. Ltd. 10/2012 - 07/2013

i) Handling Policy Proposal processing ii)
Clarifying DM & client queries regarding
operational vertical iii) Policy & AOB forms log
ins iv) Maintaining Data Base at branch level v)
Working as coordinator between client &
company in grievance cases

Project Assistant

Adept Consultants, 11/2011 - 09/2012

i) Preparation of Techno Economic Viability
Report (TEV) for the various nationalized banks
including SBI, SBM, Bank of Baroda, Bank of
India, etc. ii) These reports are one of the
major influential basis for the disbursement of
commercial loans. iii) Reports consist of
various scenarios based on factual information
collected related to project iv) Preparation of
management reports for various business
units. v) Carrying out valuation of Plant &
Machinery

Counselor & Instructor

Jyoti College of IT & Management 06/2007 - 01/2009

worked as administrator, counselor and instructor

Education

MBA/PGDM - Finance

2011

Chh.shahu institute of business education & research(SIBER)

Grade - 59%

B.Com - Commerce

2007

Shivaji University, Maharashtra

Grade - 43%